A Guide to the University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Annual Statistical Reports, 1932-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Annual Statistical Reports 1932-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-16/1/2.771
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from the Division of Continuing Education, 1977 July 11.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of annual statistical reports of the Division of Continuing Education, along with research data sheets used in compiling the reports.
Arrangement
The reports are arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Annual Reports- Statistical Data, 1920-1934, 7 folders. (Box 1)
- Report and Statistical Data re Medical Instruction, 1934 (Box 1)
- Annual Reports- Statistical Data, 1934-1938, 3 folders. (Box 1)
- Annual Reports- Statistical Data, 1938-1945, 7 folders. (Box 2)
- Annual Reports-Statistical Data, 1946-1956, 8 folders. (Box 3)
- Annual Reports- Statistical Data, 1956-1959, 3 folders. (Box 4)
- Annual Reports- National Science Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 4)
- Annual Reports- Statistical Data, 1959-1962, 3 folders. (Box 4)
- Annual Reports- Statistical Data, 1961-1964, 6 folders. (Box 5)
- Annual Reports- Statistical Data, 1963-1972, 10 folders. (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Registration and Enrollment, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 6)
- Statistical Data- Registration and Enrollment Reports, 1964-1966, 4 folders. (Box 7)
- Statistical Data- Registration and Enrollment Reports, 1965-1967, 4 folders. (Box 8)
- Statistical Data- Survey of Faculty Training- Senior Instituions (Southern Colleges and Schools Comission on Colleges), 1967 Fall (Box 8)
- Statistical data- Registration and Enrollment Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
- Statistical Data- Registration and Enrollment Reports, 1967-1970, 3 folders. (Box 9)
- Statistical Data- Micellaneous Facts Gathered on Extension Classes, Instructors, Credit Hours, etc., 1969-1970 (Box 9)
- Statistical Data- General Studies Courses, 1969-1974 (Box 9)
- Statistical Data- General Studies Forms, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
- Statistical Data- Registration and Enrollment Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
- Statistical Data- Information and Data Handling through the Registration Process, 1974 January (Box 9)